Bence Nyitrai

Studying: Web Programming with Cybersecurity

Portfolio website: https://tranquil-cannoli-742856.netlify.app

GitHub: https://github.com/nyitrai100

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/bence-nyitrai-a5033425b/

Home Address: Huddersfield, UK Telephone: 07912321302

Personal Email: nyitrai100@gmail.com University Email: u2270933@unimail.hud.ac.uk

Willing to relocate: Yes

Personal Profile

I am a dedicated student with a passion for problem-solving and innovation, specialising in advanced web development and cybersecurity. Also, I have excellent communication skills and a reputation for high-level results. Not just a talented team member, I am also a responsible and hardworking individual, with a proven ability to handle complex IT projects independently and collaboratively. Ready to contribute to enhancing team efficiency with my methodical approach, I am always aiming to contribute to the success of the organisation.

Education

BSC Web programming with Cybersecurity | University of Huddersfield (September 2022 – present)

First Year Modules	Second Year Modules (results pending)
Introduction to Data Analysis – (A)	Digital Forensics – (A)
Digital Media Asset Production– (A)	Web Development – (A)
Introduction to Web programming– (A)	Applied Data Science- (A)
Introduction to Database – (A)	Cyber Security
Computer Network Fundamentals– (A)	Visual Design
Team Project— (B)	Team Project

GSCEs | Béri Balogh Ádám High school (2010-2014)

Informatics-(A), History-(A), PE-(A), Biology-(A), Hungarian Language-(B), English-(B), Math-(C),

Achievements

- Foundational C# with Microsoft Developer Certification (2024)
- Cisco certification: Computer Network Fundamental (2023)
- NPLQ lifeguard qualification, Pool plant certificate, SELT B1, Life in the UK test (2023)
- Programming Hub certifications: HTML, CSS, JavaScript (2022)
- Electrician certificate (2022)
- NPLQ lifeguard qualification (2021)
- B1 English exam (2017)
- Recreation and Health Promotion diploma | University of Pecs, Hungary (2014-2017)

Technical Skills

- Front-end development: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Next.js, WebFlow, WordPress, Bootstrap, Tailwind, Blazor
- Back-end development: C#, PHP, NodeJS, MongoDB, MySQL,
- Cyber security: FTK Imager, Packet Tracer
- Data analysis: Excel, R

Work Experience

Leisure Attendant/ Oxygen Tower | Manchester (Jun 2022 – Aug 2023)

Effectively supervised the swimming pool and spa areas independently, managing safety protocols and responding to accidents in both the pool and gym areas. I clearly demonstrated competence in maintaining a secure environment while ensuring a positive experience for guests. Customer service skills were employed to enhance the overall guest experience.

Voluntary Experience

Web Developer / Independent / Manchester (Mar 2023 – Apr 2023)

I successfully created a portfolio website for a Hungarian businessman, showcasing adeptness in web development. I gained valuable experience in contributing effectively to the business by leveraging my sound web development skills, in this specific real-world business context. Technologies I employed include HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and jQuery.

Web Developer / Disruptive Social/ Manchester (Feb 2023 – Mar 2023)

I crafted a responsive investment calculator for Disruptive Social using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and Chart.js. The calculator was seamlessly integrated into a Webflow webpage, showcasing my technical prowess in developing solutions for business needs.

University Projects

JavaScript Mobile-Shop | (Oct 2022- Dec 2023)

I initiated and independently executed this project, utilising HTML, CSS, and JS to sculpt a responsive and engaging user interface for the JavaScript Mobile-Shop web application. With a deliberate focus on functionality, JavaScript was harnessed to systematically arrange and filter the specific items that users were seeking. This project exemplifies the practical application of my strong web development skills, showcasing a mastery in crafting dynamic and user-centric online online interactions.

Real-estate Website (Jan 2023 – May 2023)

Leading the way as the team leader in this university project, I guided a group to utilise HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and Python. Steering the team through the details of web development, these tools were skilfully used to create a smooth and lively project. As the leader, I played a cardinal role in putting together HTML for structure, CSS for looks, JavaScript for making things work; as well as Python for the behind-the-scenes functions. This leadership experience shows my ability to lead and bring together different technical skills for a successful project.

Web developer /Auction-Website/ (Feb 2023 – ongoing)

Actively contributed to an ongoing Auction website project in collaboration with a senior software engineer and an Australian company owner. My focus was on front-end development, using Next.js for dynamic web applications and utilising Tailwind for improved styling. This ongoing collaborative

effort emphasises the continuous contribution to shaping a visually appealing and functionally sound Auction website.

Web developer /Portfolio-Website/ (Oct 2023 – Oct 2023)

In the creation of a portfolio website, this project exemplified my proficiency in utilising React and applying previous CSS expertise. This project serves as a testament to its commitment to dynamic web development, emphasising both user experience and design innovation.

Leisure Time

In my free time, I prioritize fitness with regular gym and swimming sessions, and I enjoy quality moments with my girlfriend. Coding and working on personal projects are my creative outlets. Currently enrolled in a web development bootcamp on Udemy, I'm dedicated to enhancing my skills. While not part of a club, I find balance by delving into various book genres. These activities reflect my commitment to personal growth, creativity, and a well-rounded lifestyle.

References: Available on request.